cooltechzone.com 2019-12-30

# Privacy Policy | Best VPN Zone

_Your privacy is critically important to us._

It is Best VPN Zone's policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our website. This Privacy Policy applies to [https://cooltechzone.com](https://cooltechzone.com/) (hereinafter, "us", "we", or "cooltechzone"). We respect your privacy and are committed to protecting personally identifiable information you may provide us through the Website. 

We have adopted this privacy policy ("Privacy Policy") to explain what information may be collected on our Website, how we use this information, and under what circumstances we may disclose the information to third parties. This Privacy Policy applies only to information we collect through the Website and does not apply to our collection of information from other sources.

This Privacy Policy, together with the Terms and conditions posted on our Website, set forth the general rules and policies governing your use of our Website. Depending on your activities when visiting our Website, you may be required to agree to additional terms and conditions.

* * *

## Website Visitors

Like most website operators, Best VPN Zone collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Best VPN Zone's purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how Best VPN Zone's visitors use its website. From time to time, Best VPN Zone may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.

Best VPN Zone also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for logged in users and for users leaving comments on cooltechzone blog posts. Best VPN Zone only discloses logged in user and commenter IP addresses under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information as described below.

* * *

## Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information

Certain visitors to Best VPN Zone's websites choose to interact with Best VPN Zone in ways that require Best VPN Zone to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that Best VPN Zone gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. 

* * *

## Security

The security of your Personal Information is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

* * *

## Links To External Sites

Our Service may contain links to external sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third party link, you will be directed to that third party's site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy and terms and conditions of every site you visit.

We have no control over, and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third party sites, products or services.

* * *

## Aggregated Statistics

Best VPN Zone may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its website. Best VPN Zone may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, Best VPN Zone does not disclose your personally-identifying information.

* * *

## Cookies

To enrich and perfect your online experience, Best VPN Zone uses "Cookies", similar technologies and services provided by others to display personalized content, appropriate advertising and store your preferences on your computer.

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor's computer, and that the visitor's browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Best VPN Zone uses cookies to help Best VPN Zone identify and track visitors, their usage of cooltechzone, and their website access preferences. Best VPN Zone visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using Best VPN Zone's websites, with the drawback that certain features of Best VPN Zone's websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

By continuing to navigate our website without changing your cookie settings, you hereby acknowledge and agree to Best VPN Zone's use of cookies.

* * *

## Privacy Policy Changes

Although most changes are likely to be minor, Best VPN Zone may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in Best VPN Zone's sole discretion. Best VPN Zone encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us.
